STANDARD FOR LIFE
The footage you are about to watch is of a sensitive nature and although
it may not be suitable for all viewers, it is for the glory of God.
As this woman sits down at the SCOAN,
we can tell by the look on her face that she is in a great deal of pain and discomfort.
As the camera moves down here body; what is revealed is a gustily wound at the top of her thigh,
which has become cancerous.
The woman by name Adia Umina had come to the SCOAN with pelvic cancer dripping with pus.
The open sore causes Adia great pain and her face tells the sad story of what she is going through.
The pelvic cancer had already eaten deep into the flesh of her right thigh,
which hangs disfigured as the sickness digs deeper yet.
As the camera pulls out, we see that the cancer is located at the top of the thigh of her right leg.
Ordinarily someone in this condition would have little hope of recovering their leg from such an affliction.
The life depending on painful amputation to survive.
However, faith makes that which seems to be against us to be for us.
Let us hear from the woman as she waits for prayer at the SCOAN
Madam tell us what is your name.(Adia Umina)
Tell us what is the problem that brought you to SCOAN today.
Cancer in my body.
You say the cancer brought you to Synagogue today?
Yes
It is painful; l cannot sleep. I am worried and I cannot walk.
Where did you go for help?
I had been to the chemist to search for solution.
How did you know about Synagogue.
Somebody directed me to the SCOAN
I believe that God will heal me of the sickness.
With that belief in her heart that Jesus Christ was able to heal her
as she sat silently before the mountain of her life.
She was arranged in The Synagogue Church Of All Nations Prayer Line for prayer from Prophet T.B. Joshua.
Here she sat at the prayer line of Synagogue Church Of All Nations with an open wound of a pelvic cancer
praying to attract God's attention and commitment through the Man of God Prophet T.B. Joshua.
As she receives prayer in the power of the Holy Spirit she rises to her feet.
Prophet T.B. Joshua uses his hand as a point of contact and prays for her
and tells her to go for she has been set free.
Jesus Christ the miracle worker has done it again in her life.
TESTIMONY TIME
Some months later Adia Umina came back to the SCOAN
to show how the Lord Jesus Christ had performed the word of His servant and healed her body completely.
There is only a scar remaining of the once malignant pelvic cancer
which had threatened her life.
Now healed, she taps the place.
Do you feel pain?
No.
Now tell us what was the problem that brought you to SCOAN.
It is cancer
You mean pelvic cancer?
Yes
The problem is over. I am happy and I thank God.
Where did you go to look for solution to that kind of problem?
I went to hospital and spent a lot money but there was no solution.
I nearly died before I was brought here to SCOAN.
You mean to say there was no solution before you came to SCOAN? (Yes)
Madam let us see that place again.
To God be the glory.
All that remains of the life threatening sore is this thin mark on her thigh.
Who else could justly heal her?
Who else could justly restore her?
Who else could have done this but Jesus Christ?
So glad was she at the hand work of God in her life that she shows the place and taps it once again
demonstrating that there is no more pain.
Do you feel pain?
I no longer feel any pain.
Before, it was like a big hole.
My leg was nearly amputated.
With the healing complete Adia Umina then gave a testimony live at the church.
My name is Adia Umina. I am from Cross River States.
What was the problem that brought you to the SCOAN?
It was cancer.
I had been to hospital and herbalist in search of a solution.
I had spent a lot of money to the extend that I didn't have money anymore.
I nearly died.
It was my neighbour who directed me to SCOAN
When I was brought to the prayer line, Prophet T.B. Joshua prayed for me.
Prophet T.B. Joshua was used by God to heal you.
Prophet T.B. Joshua did not even touch my head,
he just stretched his hand towards me and I was healed.
So he just shook his hand towards you.
So what happened immediately?
From there , I felt coldness in my body and I was healed.
To God be the glory.
Just open that place and let us see the place where the problem was there before.
As she testifies to the congregation Adia Umina lifts up her clothes
to show the evidence of God's miracle in her life.
Now without pain she vigorously taps it
to prove beyond doubt that she is completely healed.
To God be the glory.
I don't feel pain anymore.
Put your hands together for Jesus one more time.
TT Monica Asefa